<archimate:ApplicationComponent
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Facilities and Estates Mgmt, Kinetics"
    id="id-28788"
    documentation="Manages UWE accommodation for new students when apply for accommodation after firm offer&#xA;&#xA;Used in many Universities&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;http://www.kineticsolutions.co.uk/&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Also used for catering and conferences. Dave Spiller in Facilities knows more.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;And Scott Lowson, Kinetix expert, said in Jan 2016:&#xA;&#xA;I've summarized for you Kinetix functionality for the commercial modules that we have below. I can give your a demo of the software if you wish. &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;KxConferencing&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Enquiries: Allows capture of provisional enquiry details  (eg delegate numbers, budget, start date, customer/company profile,event type etc).&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Room Diary: Screen that shows room availability (although this is only accurate for ECC rooms as Syllabus Plus is UWE's room booking system)&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Events Diary: Shows list of events for month/week/day by campus/event type&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Event Screen&#xA;&#xA;Catering: Allows booking of catering that appears in the KxCatering module used by Facilities hospitality staff.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Room/Equipment: Allows adding various types of rooms and equipment to the event.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Dialogue: A place to record customer coms, including files.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Delegates: A place to add event delegates  with various details such as arrival/departure dates, car reg, payments, and bespoke items such as dietary/medical conditions , and allocate UWE bedroom stock that is used by Accomodation Services in KxStudent.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;There is an product called KxRegistrations, that we do not have, but this will allow delegates to register for an event online, make payment and capture any details we want. It might be here that  sessions are selected. The information is added directly to the Delegates section of the event. The cost is approx £5K per year, plus installation costs. I'm not sure how inviting other attendees to accompany is possible, we would have to ask Kinetics.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Department Notes: As Dave mentioned, this is where operational info for UWE departments is left eg Room setup for CSOs, Electronic Signage, cleaning etc. These can then reproduced in daily reports for various teams.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Quotes: Allows a forecast of event sales/revenue.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Financial: Allows raising an invoice of final event revenue. With Kx financial interface the invoice can be imported to Aggresso. We do have this for KxConferencing, but accommodation use it for rents, so would only entail a configuration cost.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Mailings: Allows email and word predefined templates to be used to mail event organisers (but not delegates).&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Audit: Provides a full user audit of all event details and amendments.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Copy Event: Allows the event to be copied to new date(s).&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Booking Contract: Allows the generation and email of a pdf report, listing all event details with added sign page if required, to be sent to the event organiser (not delegate)&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;KxPlorer: A  report module that allows us to create and design our own bespoke reports from the Kx sql database. This includes delegate lists and  labels with barcodes.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;KxMarketing: We do not use this module much, but it can be used for forecasting, mails shots and contact management. Delegate lists can be imported to contact management and managed accordingly for feedback/future events via email/phone, and marketing campaigns can be created for recording mailshots etc."/>
